

Front-End Developer

Profile

I graduated from the National Defense University in July 2021. Contrary to my academic career, I've developed myself in many areas of this branch for hobby purposes since I've been extremely interested in computer and web technologies starting from my secondary school age, and I also took the opportunity to gain experience in this branch. Since I want to continue my career in this direction in the future, I continue to develop myself as a Fronted Developer and continue bootcamp processes supported by online trainings. I continue to undertake the task of web site administrator of the digital content platform Bublogta that I am the founder of

	Languages		
ingilizce B1			
	Education		
Licence, National Defense University (Defense Management) ☑ 3.17			07/2017 – 08/2021 Ankara, Turkey
High School, Karabuk High School 78.03			07/2013 – 06/2017 Karabuk, Turkey
	Skills		
HTML5	css	-	
Bootstrap Css Library	JavaS ES6+ a	Script = and Modular JS	
React JS Framework	Word!	Press = 'ooCommerce	
Web Hosting Control Panels Cpanel, Plesk, Cyberpanel	SEO	-	

Cloud Services

Experience

Front-End Developer, ID3 🛮

04/2022 – Present İstanbul, Turkey

Military Officer, Turkish Armed Force

08/2021 - Present istanbul, Turkey

Freelancer 2017 - Present

I provide freelance services in areas such as software development and WordPress software on platforms such as Bionluk and R10.net

Patika.Dev Bootcamp Acceleration Program, Patika.Dev 🛮

It is an 8-week training program that aims to improve the technical skills, algorithmic skills and professional business skills of the participants.

03/2022 - 05/2022

References

Kübra Bilğiç, Operations and Analytics Specialist, Patika.Dev kubrabilgic@patika.dev, 05077141247

Projects

Bublogta Digital Content Platform, Bublogta.com 🛭

It is a digital content platform where everyone has the opportunity to bring their ideas together with the readers on the subject they want just by registering. Everyone can create a portfolio by developing their own profile and present it to thousands of readers with Bublogta, which we have developed to acquire a digital literacy culture. I continue to be the Web Manager of Bublogta, of which I am one of the founders.

11/2019 - Present

Courses

HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, Udemy, UC-d195f4ca-bd1a-4a3d-a183-25c9b222920f

Beginner Level Frontend Web Development, ZHAH9mb ☑ HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git, JavaScript, Data Structures and Algorithms

Interests

Creating Digital Content @, Reading book, Swimming